<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0" xml:id="CV">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Joey (Joseph) Takeda's Curriculum Vitae</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p> Last generated 2023-05-15.</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Born digital, but generated using XSLT.</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <particDesc>
            <person xml:id="me">
               <persName>
                  <name>Joey (Joseph) Takeda</name>
                  <email/>
               </persName>
            </person>
         </particDesc>
      </profileDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text>
      <body>
         <listPerson>
            <person sameAs="#me">
               <education from="2022">Masters of Library and Information Science in  at <placeName>University of Alberta</placeName>.</education>
               <education from="2016" to="2021">Masters of Arts in English at <placeName>University of British Columbia</placeName>.</education>
               <education from="2012" to="2016">Bachelor of Arts (Honours) in English &amp; Women’s Studies (minor) at <placeName>University of Victoria</placeName>.</education>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2020-01">
                  <p>Developer at Digital Humanities Innovation Lab, Simon Fraser University.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2017-09" to="2018-12">
                  <p>Teaching Assistant at Department of English, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2018-01" to="2019-12">
                  <p>Lead Programmer at Linked Early Modern Drama Online, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2018-12" to="2019-12">
                  <p>Programmer at The Winnifred Eaton Archive, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2018-12" to="2019-12">
                  <p>Lead Programmer (Digital Archive) at Landscapes of Injustice, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2019-07" to="2019-12">
                  <p>Digital Humanities Consultant at Public Humanities Hub, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2014-05" to="2016-06">
                  <p>Research Assistant at The Map of Early Modern London, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2016-05" to="2019-12">
                  <p>Programmer at The Endings Project, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="paid" from="2015-05" to="2017-12">
                  <p>Junior Programmer at The Map of Early Modern London, University of Victoria .</p>
               </occupation>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Publications</head>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">From Tamagotchis to Pet Rocks: On Learning to Love Simplicity through the Endings Principles.</title>
                     <title level="m">Digital Humanities Quarterly</title> (DHQ), forthcoming.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Lines, Sydney, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Recovering a Future Artifact: <title level="m">The Winnifred Eaton Archive</title> and a Genealogy of Care.</title>
                     <title level="m">Legacy: A Journal of American Women Writers</title>, forthcoming.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Digital Lyon in Mourning.</title>
                     <title level="m">International Review of Scottish Studies</title> (IRSS), volume 47, 2022. </bibl>
                  <bibl>Davis, Leith, Taylor Breckles, Shauna Irani, Dana Graham Lai, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Emma Trotter, and Julianna Wagar. <title level="a">
                        <title level="a">Female Rebels</title>: Highlighting Women’s Voices in Robert Forbes’s <title level="a">The Lyon in Mourning</title>.</title>
                     <title level="m">International Review of Scottish Studies</title> (IRSS), volume 47, 2022. </bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Martin Holmes. <title level="a">Serverless Searching with XSLT and JavaScript: Introducing staticSearch.</title>
                     <title level="m">Proceedings of Balisage: The Markup Conference 2022</title>. Balisage Series on Markup Technologies, volume 27, 2022. </bibl>
                  <bibl>Roberts-Smith, Jennifer, Mark Kaethler, and Toby Malone with Liza Giffen, Martin Holmes, Janelle Jenstad, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Tagging Time and Space: TEI and the Canadian Stratford Festival Promptbooks.</title>
                     <title level="m">Digital Studies/le Champ Numérique</title>, volume 9, issue 1, 2019. </bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Beyond Validation: Using Programmed Diagnostics to Learn About, Monitor, and Successfully Complete Your DH Project.</title>
                     <title level="m">Digital Scholarship in the Humanities</title> (DSH), volume 34, issue supp. 1, 2019. i100–i109. </bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Making the RA Matter: Pedagogy, Interface, and Practices.</title>
                     <title level="m">Making Things and Drawing Boundaries: Experiments in the Digital Humanities</title>, edited by Jentery Sayers, University of Minnesota Press, 2018, pp. 71–85. </bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Invited Presentations</head>
                  <bibl>Chapman, Mary, Sydney Lines, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Encountering Epithets: On Encoding (and Not Encoding) Racialized Language in the Winnifred Eaton Archive.</title> Antiracist Markup Practices Symposium, Women Writers Project, Northeastern University, May 15, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Moore, Alison J., <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, and Julianna Wagar. <title level="a">Unlock Your Research Impact: Digital Humanities for the Public.</title> Knowledge Mobilization Lunch and Learn Series, Simon Fraser University Library, February 1, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Sustainable StoryMaps: A Case Study in Staticization with StoryMapJS.</title> GIS Day 2021, Simon Fraser University and the University of British Columbia, November 19, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Dowson, Rebecca, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Where Do We Go From Here? Incubating Digital Scholarship in the Library.</title> Lightning talk. The Canadian Digital Scholarship Community of Practice Meeting. October 21, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive.</title> Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive Launch, University of Victoria, March 31, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive.</title> Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive Launch, University of Victoria, March 28, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Introduction to the Digital Archive.</title> The Winnifred Eaton Archive Public Launch, University of British Columbia, September 16, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Ending MoEML.</title> Panel presentation for <title level="m">MoEML at Twenty</title> with Mark Kaethler and Janelle Jenstad. Canadian Society for Digital Humanities/Société Canadienne Des Humanités Numériques (CSDH-SCHN) Conference. Congress of the Humanities and Social Sciences, University of British Columbia, June 03, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Chapman, Mary, Sydney Lines, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">The Winnifred Eaton Archive.</title> UBC Pixelating Project Showcase, University of British Columbia, May 20, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, Tye Landels-Gruenewald, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">How To Do Things with 6000 Toponyms.</title> Presented by Janelle Jenstad and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. How To Do Things with Millions Of Words Conference, University of British Columbia, November 03, 2016.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Refereed Presentations</head>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, Leith Davis, and the Lyon in Mourning Team. <title level="a">Building Networks: The Lyon in Mourning Project and Institutional Collaborations.</title> Reviewing, Revising, and Refining Open Social Scholarship: An Implementing New Knowledge Environments (INKE) Partnership Gathering. Victoria, BC, Canada. January 17, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Granting Agency: Opportunities and Challenges of Named Grant Collaborations</title>. Keeping it ReAL 2022: LIS and Collaboration, University of British Columbia and Simon Fraser University, November 17, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Martin Holmes. <title level="a">Serverless Searching with XSLT and JavaScript</title>. Balisage: The Markup Conference 2022. August 1, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">
                        <title level="a">An Exact and Faithful Copy</title>?: Encoding, Transcribing, and Using the Digital <title level="a">Lyon in Mourning</title>
                     </title>. New Perspectives on Robert Forbes’s <title level="a">The Lyon in Mourning</title> Manuscript. Institute for Advanced Studies in the Humanities, University of Edinburgh. June 30, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Davis, Leith, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Jasmyn Bojakli, Taylor Breckles, Alyssa Bridgman, and Kaitlyn MacInnis. <title level="a">NextGen Meets OldGen: Encoding an Eighteenth-Century Metadata Project.</title> Poster Session. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2021 Conference. October 26, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Nine Projects, One Codebase: A Static Search Engine for Digital Editions.</title>  Collaboration: Digital Humanities Conference. University of British Columbia. October 31, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Joyce, Michael, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Frédérik Lesage, Michelle Levy, and Rémi Castonguay. <title level="a">Collaboration in the Middle.</title> Collaboration: Digital Humanities Conference. University of British Columbia. October 29, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Martin Holmes. <title level="a">Static Search: An Archivable and Sustainable Search Engine for the Digital Humanities.</title> DHSI Conference and Colloquium 2020. June 06, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Sydney Lines. <title level="a">Using Github and its Integrations to Create, Test, and Deploy a Digital Edition.</title> Presented by <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 19, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">The Prefabricated Website: Who Needs a Server Anyway?</title> Presented by Martin Holmes. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 19, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Brett Greatley-Hirsch, and James Mardock. <title level="a">What is a Line? Encoding and Counting Lines in Early Modern Dramatic Texts.</title> Presented by Janelle Jenstad. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 18, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Roberts-Smith, Jennifer, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Mark Kaethler, Toby Malone, and Janelle Jenstad. <title level="a">Reconceiving TEI Models of Theatrical Performance Text with Reference to Promptbooks.</title> Presented by Janelle Jenstad. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 18, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Jennifer Roberts-Smith. <title level="a">One More Time With Feeling: Revisiting XPointers to Address the Complexities of Promptbook Encoding.</title> Presented by Jennifer Roberts-Smith. Digital Humanities 2019 (DH2019) Conference. Utrecht University. July 12, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Unsettling Geologic Vision.</title> Association of Canadian College and University Teachers of English (ACCUTE) Conference. Congress of the Humanities and Social Sciences. University of British Columbia. June 03, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Why Do I Need Four Search Engines?</title> Presented by Martin Holmes. Japanese Association for Digital Humanities conference. September 13, 2018. <ref target="http://joeytakeda.github.io/pdf/JADH_2018.pdf">PDF</ref>.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">
                        <title level="a">Depth and width between the surface</title>: Reading Vertical Mobility in François Mandeville’s <title level="a">How Copper Was Discovered</title> and Marie Clements’ <title level="m">Burning Vision</title>.</title> Endnotes 2018 conference. University of British Columbia. May 05, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Rethinking Protocols: Networking, Temporality, Decolonization.</title> Qualicum History Conference. Parksville, British Columbia. January 27, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Beyond Validation: Using Programmed Diagnostics to Learn About, Monitor, and Successfully Complete Your DH Project.</title> Digital Humanities 2017 Conference. McGill University. August 11, 2017.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, Tye Landels-Gruenewald, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Mapping the STC with MoEML and DEEP.</title> Digital Humanities 2017 Conference. Presented by Tye Landels-Gruenewald and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. McGill University. August 09, 2017. <ref target="http://joeytakeda.github.io/pdf/Beyond_Validation-2017.pdf">PDF</ref>.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Fragility of Reconciliation: Reading <title level="m">The Book of Jessica</title>.</title> CSPT Graduate Conference. University of Victoria. May 05, 2017.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Viewing Jewish and Trans Identity: History, Genetics, and Jill Soloway’s <title level="m">Transparent</title>.</title> Qualicum History Conference. Parksville, British Columbia. January 28, 2017.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Invited Presentations</head>
                  <bibl>Chapman, Mary, Sydney Lines, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Encountering Epithets: On Encoding (and Not Encoding) Racialized Language in the Winnifred Eaton Archive.</title> Antiracist Markup Practices Symposium, Women Writers Project, Northeastern University, May 15, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Moore, Alison J., <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, and Julianna Wagar. <title level="a">Unlock Your Research Impact: Digital Humanities for the Public.</title> Knowledge Mobilization Lunch and Learn Series, Simon Fraser University Library, February 1, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Sustainable StoryMaps: A Case Study in Staticization with StoryMapJS.</title> GIS Day 2021, Simon Fraser University and the University of British Columbia, November 19, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Dowson, Rebecca, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Where Do We Go From Here? Incubating Digital Scholarship in the Library.</title> Lightning talk. The Canadian Digital Scholarship Community of Practice Meeting. October 21, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive.</title> Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive Launch, University of Victoria, March 31, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive.</title> Landscapes of Injustice Digital Archive Launch, University of Victoria, March 28, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Introduction to the Digital Archive.</title> The Winnifred Eaton Archive Public Launch, University of British Columbia, September 16, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Ending MoEML.</title> Panel presentation for <title level="m">MoEML at Twenty</title> with Mark Kaethler and Janelle Jenstad. Canadian Society for Digital Humanities/Société Canadienne Des Humanités Numériques (CSDH-SCHN) Conference. Congress of the Humanities and Social Sciences, University of British Columbia, June 03, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Chapman, Mary, Sydney Lines, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">The Winnifred Eaton Archive.</title> UBC Pixelating Project Showcase, University of British Columbia, May 20, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, Tye Landels-Gruenewald, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">How To Do Things with 6000 Toponyms.</title> Presented by Janelle Jenstad and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. How To Do Things with Millions Of Words Conference, University of British Columbia, November 03, 2016.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Refereed Presentations</head>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, Leith Davis, and the Lyon in Mourning Team. <title level="a">Building Networks: The Lyon in Mourning Project and Institutional Collaborations.</title> Reviewing, Revising, and Refining Open Social Scholarship: An Implementing New Knowledge Environments (INKE) Partnership Gathering. Victoria, BC, Canada. January 17, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Granting Agency: Opportunities and Challenges of Named Grant Collaborations</title>. Keeping it ReAL 2022: LIS and Collaboration, University of British Columbia and Simon Fraser University, November 17, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Martin Holmes. <title level="a">Serverless Searching with XSLT and JavaScript</title>. Balisage: The Markup Conference 2022. August 1, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">
                        <title level="a">An Exact and Faithful Copy</title>?: Encoding, Transcribing, and Using the Digital <title level="a">Lyon in Mourning</title>
                     </title>. New Perspectives on Robert Forbes’s <title level="a">The Lyon in Mourning</title> Manuscript. Institute for Advanced Studies in the Humanities, University of Edinburgh. June 30, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Davis, Leith, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Jasmyn Bojakli, Taylor Breckles, Alyssa Bridgman, and Kaitlyn MacInnis. <title level="a">NextGen Meets OldGen: Encoding an Eighteenth-Century Metadata Project.</title> Poster Session. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2021 Conference. October 26, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Nine Projects, One Codebase: A Static Search Engine for Digital Editions.</title>  Collaboration: Digital Humanities Conference. University of British Columbia. October 31, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Joyce, Michael, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Frédérik Lesage, Michelle Levy, and Rémi Castonguay. <title level="a">Collaboration in the Middle.</title> Collaboration: Digital Humanities Conference. University of British Columbia. October 29, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Martin Holmes. <title level="a">Static Search: An Archivable and Sustainable Search Engine for the Digital Humanities.</title> DHSI Conference and Colloquium 2020. June 06, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Sydney Lines. <title level="a">Using Github and its Integrations to Create, Test, and Deploy a Digital Edition.</title> Presented by <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 19, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">The Prefabricated Website: Who Needs a Server Anyway?</title> Presented by Martin Holmes. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 19, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Brett Greatley-Hirsch, and James Mardock. <title level="a">What is a Line? Encoding and Counting Lines in Early Modern Dramatic Texts.</title> Presented by Janelle Jenstad. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 18, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Roberts-Smith, Jennifer, <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>, Mark Kaethler, Toby Malone, and Janelle Jenstad. <title level="a">Reconceiving TEI Models of Theatrical Performance Text with Reference to Promptbooks.</title> Presented by Janelle Jenstad. Text Encoding Initiative (TEI) 2019 Conference. University of Graz. September 18, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>, and Jennifer Roberts-Smith. <title level="a">One More Time With Feeling: Revisiting XPointers to Address the Complexities of Promptbook Encoding.</title> Presented by Jennifer Roberts-Smith. Digital Humanities 2019 (DH2019) Conference. Utrecht University. July 12, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Unsettling Geologic Vision.</title> Association of Canadian College and University Teachers of English (ACCUTE) Conference. Congress of the Humanities and Social Sciences. University of British Columbia. June 03, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Why Do I Need Four Search Engines?</title> Presented by Martin Holmes. Japanese Association for Digital Humanities conference. September 13, 2018. <ref target="http://joeytakeda.github.io/pdf/JADH_2018.pdf">PDF</ref>.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">
                        <title level="a">Depth and width between the surface</title>: Reading Vertical Mobility in François Mandeville’s <title level="a">How Copper Was Discovered</title> and Marie Clements’ <title level="m">Burning Vision</title>.</title> Endnotes 2018 conference. University of British Columbia. May 05, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Rethinking Protocols: Networking, Temporality, Decolonization.</title> Qualicum History Conference. Parksville, British Columbia. January 27, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Holmes, Martin, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Beyond Validation: Using Programmed Diagnostics to Learn About, Monitor, and Successfully Complete Your DH Project.</title> Digital Humanities 2017 Conference. McGill University. August 11, 2017.</bibl>
                  <bibl>Jenstad, Janelle, Tye Landels-Gruenewald, and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. <title level="a">Mapping the STC with MoEML and DEEP.</title> Digital Humanities 2017 Conference. Presented by Tye Landels-Gruenewald and <ref target="#me">Joey Takeda</ref>. McGill University. August 09, 2017. <ref target="http://joeytakeda.github.io/pdf/Beyond_Validation-2017.pdf">PDF</ref>.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">The Fragility of Reconciliation: Reading <title level="m">The Book of Jessica</title>.</title> CSPT Graduate Conference. University of Victoria. May 05, 2017.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <ref target="#me">Takeda, Joey</ref>. <title level="a">Viewing Jewish and Trans Identity: History, Genetics, and Jill Soloway’s <title level="m">Transparent</title>.</title> Qualicum History Conference. Parksville, British Columbia. January 28, 2017.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Guest Lectures</head>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Encoding Screenplays.</title> ENGL 501: Digital Methods for Literary Study: Recovering Early Chinese Canadian Literature and History, University of British Columbia, March 17, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Text Encoding and Textual Editing.</title> ENGL 820: Eighteenth-Century Media: An Embodied Humanities Approach, Simon Fraser University, November 11, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Textual Editing.</title> ENGL 490: Digital Methods for Literary Study: Recovering Early Asian North American Literature, University of British Columbia, October 28, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Text Encoding.</title> ENGL 820: Studies in Print Culture Theory, Simon Fraser University, November 23, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Remediating Bills of Mortality.</title> ENGL 362: Popular Literature in the Renaissance, University of Victoria, February 3, 2016.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Encoding Maps.</title> SLST 481: Existence and Anxiety in Dostoevsky, University of Victoria, January 29, 2015.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Workshops</head>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">How to End Your Digital Project (three day workshop).</title> Co-taught with Janelle Jenstad. DH@Guelph 2023 Workshop Series, University of Guelph, May 10–12, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Unlocking XML Data with XPath.</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, March 29, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to the Text Encoding Initiative (TEI): What is it and why should I care?</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, October 26, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Minimal Computing, or When Wordpress No Longer Sparks Joy.</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, November 17, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to the Text Encoding Initiative: What is it and why should I care?</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, July 7, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Encoding for Literary Studies.</title> Department of English Language and Literatures, University of British Columbia, April 15, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">So I Want To Use the TEI . . . Now What?</title> Pixelating DH Mixer and Workshop, University of British Columbia, October 25, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">What is the TEI and Why Should I Care?</title> Pixelating DH Mixer and Workshop, University of British Columbia, September 20, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Ending Your Digital Humanities Project from the Start.</title> Pixelating DH Mixer and Workshop, University of British Columbia, June 28, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to TEI Projects Workshop (full day workshop).</title> Co-taught with Janelle Jenstad. TEI 2017 conference,  University of Victoria, November 11, 2017.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Teaching Assistantships</head>
                  <bibl>ENGL 110: Introduction to Media Studies. University of British Columbia, September–December, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>ENGL 110: Indigenous and Multicultural Literature in Canada. University of British Columbia, September–December, 2017.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Guest Lectures</head>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Encoding Screenplays.</title> ENGL 501: Digital Methods for Literary Study: Recovering Early Chinese Canadian Literature and History, University of British Columbia, March 17, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Text Encoding and Textual Editing.</title> ENGL 820: Eighteenth-Century Media: An Embodied Humanities Approach, Simon Fraser University, November 11, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Textual Editing.</title> ENGL 490: Digital Methods for Literary Study: Recovering Early Asian North American Literature, University of British Columbia, October 28, 2021.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Text Encoding.</title> ENGL 820: Studies in Print Culture Theory, Simon Fraser University, November 23, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Remediating Bills of Mortality.</title> ENGL 362: Popular Literature in the Renaissance, University of Victoria, February 3, 2016.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Encoding Maps.</title> SLST 481: Existence and Anxiety in Dostoevsky, University of Victoria, January 29, 2015.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Workshops</head>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">How to End Your Digital Project (three day workshop).</title> Co-taught with Janelle Jenstad. DH@Guelph 2023 Workshop Series, University of Guelph, May 10–12, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Unlocking XML Data with XPath.</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, March 29, 2023.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to the Text Encoding Initiative (TEI): What is it and why should I care?</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, October 26, 2022.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Minimal Computing, or When Wordpress No Longer Sparks Joy.</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, November 17, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to the Text Encoding Initiative: What is it and why should I care?</title> Digital Humanities Workshop Skill Series, Simon Fraser University Library, July 7, 2020.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to Encoding for Literary Studies.</title> Department of English Language and Literatures, University of British Columbia, April 15, 2019.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">So I Want To Use the TEI . . . Now What?</title> Pixelating DH Mixer and Workshop, University of British Columbia, October 25, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">What is the TEI and Why Should I Care?</title> Pixelating DH Mixer and Workshop, University of British Columbia, September 20, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Ending Your Digital Humanities Project from the Start.</title> Pixelating DH Mixer and Workshop, University of British Columbia, June 28, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>
                     <title level="a">Introduction to TEI Projects Workshop (full day workshop).</title> Co-taught with Janelle Jenstad. TEI 2017 conference,  University of Victoria, November 11, 2017.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <listBibl>
                  <head>Teaching Assistantships</head>
                  <bibl>ENGL 110: Introduction to Media Studies. University of British Columbia, September–December, 2018.</bibl>
                  <bibl>ENGL 110: Indigenous and Multicultural Literature in Canada. University of British Columbia, September–December, 2017.</bibl>
               </listBibl>
               <note>
                  <list>
                     <head>Grants</head>
                     <item>
                Co-Applicant. SSHRC Connection Grant, <title level="a">Onoto Watanna’s CATTLE at 100: Indomitable Women in the West During the Chinese Exclusion Era,</title> $24,983. (Principal Investigator: Mary Chapman)
             (<date when="2021-05">2021-05</date>)</item>
                     <item>Collaborator. SSHRC Partnership Engage Grant, <title level="a">Engaging Public and Academic Audiences to Recover Lost Voices of Scottish History: <title level="a">The Lyon in Mourning</title> Manuscript and the Jacobite Networks of the 1745 Rising</title>, $18,000. (Principal Investigator: Leith Davis) (<date when="2020-05">2020-05</date>)</item>
                  </list>
               </note>
               <note>
                  <list>
                     <head>Awards</head>
                     <item>SSHRC Canadian Graduate Scholarship-Masters (<date when="2016">2016</date>)</item>
                     <item>University of Victoria Department of English Medal of Excellence (<date when="2016">2016</date>)</item>
                     <item>Frank Hori Foundation Scholarship (<date when="2015">2015</date>)</item>
                     <item>Allardice Lancaster Scholarship (<date when="2015">2015</date>)</item>
                     <item>Jamie Cassels Undergraduate Research Award (<date when="2015">2015</date>)</item>
                     <item>Purves-Cordonier Prize (<date when="2015">2015</date>)</item>
                     <item>Frank Hori Foundation Scholarship (<date when="2014">2014</date>)</item>
                     <item>Grant McOrmond Scholarship in English (<date when="2014">2014</date>)</item>
                     <item>John Peter Memorial Scholarship (<date when="2014">2014</date>)</item>
                     <item>University of Victoria Excellence Scholarship (<date when="2012">2012</date>)</item>
                  </list>
               </note>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2023-05">
                  <p>Member at Public Knowledge Project Technical Committee.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2023-01">
                  <p>Elected Member at TEI-C Technical Council.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2022-05">
                  <p>Peer Reviewer at The Advanced Research Consortium.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2021-02">
                  <p>International Advisory Board Member at TEI By Example.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2019-01">
                  <p>Technical Director at The Winnifred Eaton Archive.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2019-01" to="2020-02">
                  <p>Peer Reviewer at Journal of the Text Encoding Initiative.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2018-09" to="2019-09">
                  <p>Member at Works in Progress Committee, English Graduate Caucus, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2018-09" to="2018-12">
                  <p>Union Representative at English Graduate Caucus, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2017-09" to="2018-09">
                  <p>Communications Coordinator at English Graduate Caucus, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2016-09" to="2017-06">
                  <p>Co-organizer at Endnotes Graduate Conference, University of British Columbia.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2015-09" to="2016-06">
                  <p>Editor-in-chief at The Albatross English Undergraduate Journal, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2015-09" to="2016-06">
                  <p>Executive Editor at The Warren Undergraduate Review, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2014-09" to="2015-06">
                  <p>Vice-President of Academic Affairs at English Students’ Association, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
               <occupation type="unpaid" from="2014-09" to="2015-06">
                  <p>Criticism Editor at The Warren Undergraduate Review, University of Victoria.</p>
               </occupation>
            </person>
         </listPerson>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
