<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cv xmlns="http://joeytakeda.github.io/ns/">
    <name id="me">Elspeth Gow</name>
    <phone>250-589-8650</phone>
    <email>elspeth.gow@gmail.com</email>
    
    <education>
        <title>Education</title>
        <degree from="2013" to="2017">
            <degree_name>Bachelor of Arts, History (Honours)</degree_name>
            <institution>University of Victoria, Victoria, British Columbia</institution>
            
        </degree>
    </education>
    <awards>
        <title>Awards</title>
        <award when="2017">Social Sciences and Humanities Masters Research Grant</award>
        <award when="2016">Harper Scholarship in History</award>
       <award when="2016">Charlotte S.M. Girard Book Prize in French History</award>
        <award when="2015">Willard E. Ireland Scholarship in History</award>
        <award when="2015">President's Scholarship</award>
        <award when="2014">Norah Lugrin Shaw and Wendell Burrill Shaw Memorial Scholarship</award>
    </awards>
    <employment>
        <title>Experience</title>
        <job from="2016-05" to="2016-09">
            <job_title>Walking Tour Guide</job_title>
            <workplace>Architectural Institute of British Columbia, Victoria BC</workplace>
            <desc>I lead two-hour architectural walking tours of up to thirty people through downtown Victoria,
                Chinatown, and James Bay, which gave me excellent public speaking skills, administrative skills, and
                independent work ethic. I was required to manage all tours run out of Victoria by the AIBC and manage the marketing of the tours through online media and posters. I also conducted independent research of
                architectural and social historical moments in Victoria's history.</desc>
        </job>
        <job from="2014-05" to="2015-09">
            <job_title>Costumed Historical Interpreter</job_title>
            <workplace>Fort Edmonton Park, Edmonton AB</workplace>
            <desc>During two summer seasons employed at Fort Edmonton Park, my job was to deliver quality programs to the general public, offering both tours and drop-in programs. I performed historical vignettes for visitors and gained a mastery of educational and interpretive theory when engaging the public. I also gained independent research skills and the ability to access and navigate municipal and
                provincial archives in order to gather information on Edmonton's settlement narrative and write
                programs for the public. I have a strong command of Western Canadian history.</desc>
        </job>
        <job from="2013-05" to="2013-09">
            <job_title>Natural and Human History Interpreter</job_title>
            <workplace>John Walter Museum and Muttart Conservatory, Edmonton AB</workplace>
            <desc>I organized and lead day-camps, planned educational drop-ins, and scheduled programs on
                human and natural history. I also conducted independent research on both Edmonton's settlement
                narrative (John Walter Museum) and botany and biology (Muttart Conservatory).</desc>
        </job>
    </employment>
    <service>
        <title>Service</title>
        <job from="2016" to="2017">
            <job_title>Executive Editor</job_title>
            <workplace>The Warren Undergraduate Review</workplace>
        </job>
    </service>
    <publications>
        <title>Publications</title>
        <publication><ref target="#me">Gow, Elspeth</ref>. "Displaying the Inscrutable at the Royal BC Museum’s <title level="m">Chinatown</title> Gallery." <title level="m">The Corvette Undergraduate History Journal</title>. Vol 4 no. 1, 2017.</publication>
        
        
        
    </publications>
    <conferences>
        <title>Conference Presentations</title>
        <!--        TODO: DH, ILSA.-->
        <conference><ref target="#me">Gow, Elspeth</ref>. "Reconciliation in Theatres of Living History, Particularly Fort Edmonton Park." Qualicum History conference. Parksville, British Columbia. January 28, 2017.</conference>
           </conferences>


    <references>
        <title>References</title>
<!--<reference>
<name>Lynne Marks</name>
<role>Associate Professor, History, University of Victoria</role>
<email>lsmarks@uvic.ca</email>
<phone>250-721-7392</phone>
</reference>-->
<reference>
<name>Sara Beam</name>
<role>Associate Professor, History, University of Victoria</role>
<email>sbeam@uvic.ca</email>
<phone>250-721-7406</phone>
</reference>
<!--<reference>
<name>Hélène Cazes</name>
<role>Associate Professor, French, University of Victoria</role>
<email>hcazes@uvic.ca</email>
<phone>250-721-7367</phone>
</reference>-->
        <reference>
            <name>Jordan Stanger-Ross</name>
            <role>Associate Professor, History, University of Victoria</role>
            <email>jstross@uvic.ca</email>
            <phone>250-721-7283</phone>
        </reference>
       
    </references>
</cv>
